This morning, tomorrow
you will get another level
called the one in the summaries
or overview in the west, which should be in what
we have done in the last 8 years.
I'm finished with that here, but we should have gone through it
continuously. But
I was, that's very unusual.
I think I only have 78. The right to
check for yourself where to see.
Okay, you're in Alex's plans. What I think
we're starting is
an overview of the eight years. You can
decide.
Studying law is, of course, a tent.
Cher, economics, business lawyer.
Decide. The basic thing is, because it's
a channel. You can learn.
Concert.
That's also a meditation specialist.
Example: like Constantin Kollmann.
Sailors become
specialists. Specifically, meditation.
We do two nations that
everyone has and doesn't have to anymore. And
you want the special teams and
special Just Dance.
His specialty turned to become a master.
Some have that. It's interesting and
not able to put a stop to it.
So, between one week and
three years, you can become a station
specialist teacher.
I think I'm actually saying that with
specialists.
The camera is the greatest
comment on the article.  has a full
list of master-crafted solutions. You
can have a normal education on the path
because you can have a basic education, and
what can you do? You're pretty sure that's
something. Then you can go to
China and have a
basic education,
and then we'll start the masterclasses. The
commitment started last November
here in
November, so far so good that I
need five years to specialize. They want to
come every autumn. After your
comment about it, you're in Hamburg. From
Madonna's most famous book, that's really, really. You do
n't have to have this
master training either, that
meditation, or now we'll continue.
Now, new topics.
Look for BBM spaces.
Have you found it? It's unique. It's
very distinctive. The word exists
only once in the text. BBM spaces.
You've never seen it before, neither have I.
He's talking about the first of the six
negative main emotions, and that was
craving in school. Now that
he has the whole outline of the
training, the five topics, the
four and a half schools, now
you can recognize how many
different levels he's
taught. You get a lesson,
and everyone sees a  On a different level, using the
same words, in lower schools,
when you study desire, it means: don't buy
anything new, do
n't have nice clothes, live in
a cave. It
's okay, there's a place for that,
especially if you're
easily distracted by material things. Right now,
if you lose yourself in making money
and suddenly lose it, suddenly die,
you lose everything. For
these people, that teaching is correct.
But at a higher level,
we want to learn how to
share with other people. So, desire
is the opposite of sharing.
It's okay if a man likes chocolate chip cookies,
but if you like them, then don't refuse
to share them with others
because then you won't get them
anymore. Desire is actually stupidity
and not
intelligent desire. It's when Keller
spreads his cookies because he wants more cookies,
and there's nothing wrong with that.
In reality, you can't get anything in
your life, not even a tissue,
if you don't share it with
others. Intelligence isn't
desire because money makes you happy.
If we now desire as the
Attachment to your body is described. There are
traditional meditations in
the tenants' schools, and we will talk about them today.
It sounds similar to "kangaroo" in
Australia. Left are human
dictionary. That you come to my office
means beautiful. That is the ugliness
meditation, a meditation about
seeing the ugliness of things. A famous
example of this is going to the cinema. Ten people went.
He teaches that here, not here. Yes,
he doesn't teach it here, but you can do
the meditation for us.
It is an old meditation from the
media, from the Abitur.
What do you call it again? What is the name of
the disease? You lose your legs,
then turn. You imagine
that there is a small green dot between your eyes that keeps
spreading. Its skin inside,
your skin comes off, and the skull
bones, and then you go over
the whole skull as it dissolves,
and then you have no skin and no
flesh anymore, and then you go into your
body until a whole body
is rotten, and then you do your
meditation. It gets old and he  It gets
tattered, and then the building around you
gets old and collapses. It
will eventually come together.
We have all the buildings
here, actually made of Adobe. It's
called brick, and the idea
was that if we all don't stay here long, there will be
reason to worry. When
will the yields simply return to the
earth?
However, the house, for example, collapsed recently,
and it simply returns to
the earth. In the meditation,
it's like an atomic bomb.
Eventually, the house gets old and it will
disintegrate, and then you go to the highway,
and all the cars disintegrate, and then to
Tucson. Eventually,
it will be empty.
Then there won't be enough water for
cruisers, and they will move away.
You do this meditation, then you go
to California, and California, and
New York. Then you dry up the ocean
outside, all the fish die, and the ocean
is gone. And that should
eliminate desires. And that means the
bone meditation speaks here
about another:
how can you overcome desires? People,
you can do the meditation with Super.
What does that mean? What is it?  Marco, you
peel off the skin when you're not
looking at someone else's wife,
and darkness until you're very attracted
to her. Then imagine in your
meditation how you give her the
final coppery appearance of the
half centimeters under the skin.
It's really a repulsive
meditation, the disgust meditation. You peel off
the skin in a meditation. His
meditation is so strong
that every time you see this
woman, this man, she's
married to someone else, then
you will simply
recoil.
But it's our school. It might
not work. That's
the definition of the lower school. It might
work, but maybe
not.
A better meditation would be the higher
school.
You are really the adulterer with
these people. Will it be karma
that you never have a reliable
partner in your life, and then
you will know that this married woman
or married man is no longer
possible? It's simply stupid to do it.
This is a much better method than
peeling off the skin.
Sometimes it will work like
aspirin.
Sometimes this
meditation works with the hate.  Sowing and
the name is steak meditation.
Someday they will die and
evening falls. In England, there wasn't
quartering. They tied chainmail's arms and
feet tightly to four horses,
and they distributed the people
and hung the parts in
four different cities to
represent the punishment. And sometimes
they left them hanging for five years,
and it's really very
repulsive to see.
It's called quartering, and the four parts are 110.
And then you hang one part of it
in the city for a year so that all the other
people know
what happens. But we will
all be quartered eventually. The woman
you try to steal from her husband,
or the husband you
want to take away from the woman, will be
quartered just the same. It's just meat,
and that helps you to no longer have desires,
but it only works sometimes. Together they
always work, sometimes they work. That's why it's bad.
The school was... I don't know the word, the word doesn't know it.
I looked it up,
and that means they will
also rot. The skin...  Great nose, wonderfully
colorful ears, when they
rot in a box someday, you
imagine, my father always said,
I was 18 back then,
he always said, if you fall in love with a
girl, then he also looks at her mother, a
lawyer, that's what she'll become, meaning
your skin will rot in the last box, so if, so if
you want to commit adultery,
then imagine how the skin
rots, these people say, perceive them in a
certain way, and
it's one of the five piles, and that
means the bones, when everything
is rotten, man, then I think of my mother,
I think all that's left of her
are bones in a sack, when I dig up
her coffin, there will
probably only be bones,
it will look just like
someone else's bones, I
wouldn't recognize that it's my
mother anymore, and the woman he
wants to have an affair with,
that's just it, in the end he will be nothing more,
she will only be bones, so then
it's not sexy anymore except on Halloween,
there's another one  Further
teachings about these meditations, the
viola parameters in the course and
investigators away, but they present it very
well and there are new steps to
this adultery meditation. There are new
steps, he mentioned a few more of them.
If you teach the new steps
from the corner meditation, then
they also say for each step what
the antidote is for. And so there are
new steps of the meditation and
each step solves a particular
problem, and I will now explain
these new steps to you exactly, which is why it takes so long
until we
are slowly finished.
Here are the new number one: if you,
if you approach it from the body, like Tim Cook,
her breasts, her hips, her muscles, then this
is the meditation. Imagine
how everything rots: the breasts, the hips, the
muscles.
So if you have a breast or biceps
problem with a good person, then
imagine how it rots
after they have died or how the
breasts fall off. Does it make you happy?
It is simply disgusting, but that is
another meditation, number two.
If you are sexually attracted to her or want to have sex
with him or her, who
is already married, Toshiba will introduce
all the larvae into his
body, into the
body you also allow to enter
if you want that, imagine
how the larvae and worms
penetrate this body, understand? You
are not the only one who wants to
introduce the larvae into this person.
The larvae are these white things that are a
bit like worms. There are worms in the
earth, everywhere
on his skin are fly eggs, and
if you die today, they will eat each other. They will penetrate
similarly.
You have them, you have them, they are
already running on your skin. You could
be her dinner today if
you are attracted to the smell of this person, to
their scent.
It is called menstrual blood, has Ferrari,
and down below, you smell it. Then it is
like the unconscious attraction is when
the walls, the pheromone, he is, and if
you have this problem, then imagine
how  It smells when the water and the
rider from the body of this passion
smell. There are
many people who say that there is a
repulsive
smell all over the world when the
secretions leave the body of a dead
person.
I had a meeting with one of the
richest men in the world and with the
daughter of Hewlett Packard, and she
wanted to support one of our projects.
I was a monk
in a temple, and one of my friends
died, and I really freaked out
because I thought, oh, this
woman can support it for hundreds of years.
But I have to go to a
funeral,
so I canceled and went to
the funeral. He was a
good friend. He was on the metal
table, and they do it. They make the
room very cold, and I went,
and there was the man lying naked
on this metal table. It's not cold,
and he just answered. And they
also do a bloodletting and replace it
with a form of alcohol, and they
just performed the bloodletting.
So they make sure you don't
stink so much. They really have to drain the blood
quickly so that  It didn't falter
and it was incredible, I really freaked out.
I was supposed to do his bath prayers
and I spent two or three hours
reciting the Bardot prayers. That was
really hard. If you're attracted by the scent of
a person's body or perfume,
and then imagine how they
smell two days after they died,
number four.
So if the person I'm talking about has ten pieces of jewelry—
earrings, necklace—then
you see the skin.
That's when you do the red stick
meditation. Especially in the
old text, it says that if you're also
attracted by their fashion style, the kind that's
so cool in the 20s, the ones who ask about such
cool things, then look at the
decoration of the red stick, it's repulsive, disgusting. Yes, that's how it's supposed to be
if you're attracted by their skin.
If it's very pale,
very pure skin, Mexican women
have this golden sheen on their
skin. So if you're attracted by the color of their
skin,
then the green stuff
[music],
then imagine that...  This fungus
spreads across the entire skin,
and the skin turns green. You
know what I mean?
The skin becomes difficult to work with, the green stuff in the ducts,
and then it falls off. It becomes difficult
and green, and then it falls off. So, if
you're attracted to the color, imagine
it's green like an old banana. And
if you're attracted to muscles, it
means strongly built.
In India, it's still the case that if
you're fat, it's considered beautiful,
like in Europe 500 years ago, because
it means you have money. It means you do
n't have to go hungry.
Anyone who was really fat was
considered more attractive. In America
today, it's exactly the opposite.
You have to be healthy and slim, and it's
sometimes beautiful, annoying, beautiful. It
changes over time. Back then, being
strong and fat was considered beautiful. And if you
're attracted to the body, then just imagine
how this body
is eaten by beetles and mice.
After they die, you'll be gone.
That's exactly the intention. It requires a
lot of imagination. You have to...
Even
we test it quite well. If you're
attracted to someone until you don't see the flesh,
and if you've studied Buddhism for a long time,
it's really difficult to be
sexually attracted to someone because you
look at them, and Dexter, one of the red-
greens,
I think that's why
people urgently need it because then they forget who's
really there. In higher school,
you can be attractive forever, that's
the goal of higher school,
you can be beautiful forever, and you do
n't have to plant the seeds
and have the super sexy body forever,
and it's good that way. That's
panic because we feel this
possibility that we will be
angels someday, and I think that's the reason why
other
people look at us.
You still have two arms, two legs,
you still have a head. In
higher school, you should really
make a plan for an
immortal body, for
a living diamond, super sexy, super
attracted. The chikyu, if you're attracted to the way
someone moves, the way they
walk down the street, and the guy, the
beauty of the movement,
then you do that with the four parts, like that.
lets the arm go, the legs fall off,
his arms will separate from his body,
and the feet from
one side, just don't be
dressed the way she
wants to move her arms and legs. Eventually, they will fall off the
body,
they will separate from the body.
Healed in the body, the bones are, and the most
attractive thing is the teeth, such
wonderfully beautiful white teeth. The forms of
the bones, like delicate
ballet films, decrease
in some countries. In some countries,
when they choose children for the Olympic
Games,
then they look, then they measure the
bones and make a prediction of what
that child will look like. So if
you are attracted to the bone parts, right down to
the teeth,
which meditation, the skeleton meditation,
I believe doing it with the skull
is the most powerful, Chelsea, who as a
skeleton in front of
these wonderful white teeth of this
sexy model, will be no matter what, in a skull,
sometime in Saarland, the last one in India,
in ancient India, they burned the
dead, they burned the corpses. It's like this
if you are very special  Attracted to the skin
and shape of a person,
then imagine the cremation, like how
the rich burns, like this
skin, like this ebony skin, and this
wonderful body, the shape of this
body burns. During the funeral,
it's cool.
As a connoisseur, Burgsee awarded prizes.
Unfortunately, I wasn't there. I want to go to India; it was
great, they said.
The skull fell out of the step
and rolled onto the... as it often does,
people rolled like that, and everyone freaked out.
And the skull of our
lamer is rolling towards us,
and so it will be. We will all be cremated
someday. Listen, beaten again. Good
that
you can try out these mutations,
especially if he is attracted to the
partner of another partner
or if he clings too much to your
own partner. Our
school is... sometimes it works, sometimes it does
n't. That's
the lower school for me. The higher
school always works. The higher
school works. You might as
well make the seeds for a living
diamond body and not these stupid
meditations. Here were... speaking of
And people don't talk about this in
teacher training, but in
essay training, it's also your job to learn about
our schools.
You also have to learn about our schools,
why Waters invented it for a
specific person, someone might
need it. There are
different ones, there are different
medications, or sisters, for example,
and they gave her more vitamin
D, and it made her even sicker.
I think they even
removed her kidney because it was too much vitamin D.
Different vitamins work differently in
different bodies. We
have others. You will eventually
meet someone, a student, who needs exactly this
meditation. The other woman
attracts me so much, and then Daniel says, "
I'm learning the meditation now in nine
parts.
Learn everything, all schools, because you
might meet someone who
needs exactly this." It's nice
to have a big toolbox.
I have a friend who is already 66
years old, but he always uses new tools.
Scratching his nose, wait a minute, I then have to do that,
and that's exactly how it should be.
You have every tool in one
toolbox.
You can't use the meditation for 15 years,
and  Then you meet
Yemen, and then you take out this exact
meditation and teach it to
everyone. If the mother taught it,
then it's helpful for someone.
We're now at the two main
negative emotions. There are
six main negative
emotions, and we'll also do
meditations on them. If they
are Jonas's main emotions, then Lucy has
these 84,000 bad ones every day. And in
Buddhism,
then someone said, or I
can  I didn't think of the 64,000, then
I said okay, then I'll give you
this current top ten list: 4 for the
body, 4 for language, 3 for the mind.
They're in the top ten because you do them
all every day, all day long,
not just once or twice. It's the same with
80,000 negative emotions. If they
're in the top 6, then you have to do them all every
day. There are
these 20 secondary negative
feelings,
and he named them, but he did
n't explain them. That's why I
asked what she's teaching us tomorrow. Do
you have enough time for that?
He'll give us these 20 tomorrow's
lesson, and he thinks, "Have I
already had these this year?" and talks about them.
You're going to embarrass yourself.
Maybe I can share a copy of her
with you tomorrow.
[Music]
So don't read the list, but
actually talk about each one so far
because we don't know if all
people have had the same experiences.
Okay, we might not
manage all six by tomorrow, but you do
the 20 times. Number two is annoying. The
definition is you.  Can you
be angry at people? You can
be angry
at the weather, traffic, shoes, finances.
You can be angry about anything. We
are so flexible, we change our anger
quite flexibly.
You can even be angry at your
anger.
That's happened to me too. It's called
an angry spirit, an angry spirit. To
hurt oneself, the spirit, the opposite
of Jambo. It's true, like sandpaper,
little. It's not nice to touch.
What happened? Pitt's name in and
monastery, Papa. Then I came into the party.
Rough skin, so my skin isn't soft. It's a
gift. Was the most famous nickname. Went there
and they had a debate
competition. We had dinner.
They wanted to entertain us and
they wanted to impress us because we
paid for the whole meal. And they let
everyone today. We made
them all fried.
They were supposed to debate to show
how cool they are because we
pay for everything. If you take a book to the beach
resort, into the hot to pray.
He had thought wisely about dinner
and said...  cheap cheap cheap fourth time
stupid are stupid to be and believe
what the nickname was has the next
20 years fried momo and the word
here is your mind becomes like sandpaper
annoying it's not nice to touch
the opposite in Sanskrit is some and
he who speaks softly that Munch's scream be
very soft
mind is soft Munch's mind
times shortly after the number two
you want to hurt someone you
want to hurt them my specialty is
a special form of aggression
you ask someone for a donation and they
say that ok and then you say it's okay
I'll pay for it
I won't eat for weeks but that
's okay
I'll just starve for a week
I'll pay for myself don't worry you
you have the right to
say no I'll probably have to stay in bed
and that is to
attack someone with sweet words
that it's passive aggression and everyone has
their own specialty and that
I have long we need to
figure this out there are many
different ways to
attack someone mine  Do you grab someone
with a smile? How do you get this room?
Spirit, July, unwind, and hit
a trick. What carries an organist?
Emotion. What you're the word. In German,
it means who presses a button. Worthy, tore his buttons. There are six buttons in every human being, and we will study them. It's your next six ways to press a person's buttons, and that means someone. You see, you
see someone. Only, there is someone you do
n't like. As long as they are not there,
everything is wonderful.
But when they show up at a party,
they have been invited by the idiots there,
and the Baltic Sea, and a whole evening
is ruined. Why did they
invite me? Last year,
if that is the first war
I am teaching you, the first carrier for
a negative feeling is only the
attendance list, or the person you do
n't like, or the presence of a
married woman. If you
are attracted to her, the presence is the
first carrier. What is the antidote for this?
Avoid it.
It is the ultimate antidote. No, is
it an antidote? Then you must
say immediately, but you must...  Lower
school, being a bachelor, trying to
avoid all women, trying to
avoid all people, really
irritating them in other states, and
then I say beforehand that seeing the plane,
that's the method of a lower school,
but it's a method of
dealing with negative emotions, and it takes over
a large part in Vienna,
concentric circles,
if you never leave the monastery, what
Sony, a woman, meet,
that never demands,
Bachelor, had this week, meet, and he laughed when
he heard that, the
women deliver the milk to the
monastery in the morning, and if you came, then they meet,
because if a woman, if
a woman enters the monastery in 100 years,
the karma, then you will meet this woman,
and that is definitely our
school, and if you say, I will never
talk to these people again, then
you meet them on the plane,
I spent the whole day for a
wedding ceremony with this couple,
and they would have been scared, and I did
n't actually want to
stay for an hour, and she had planned such a big ceremony,
I was 66 days later, they got
divorced, and then it was  I was on the
plane and the woman preferred to
sit more and cried the whole flight.
I can't do anything about it, I
only married you. I have a
new rule: if people get
divorced a year
before I married them,
they have to show $10,000 because I'll do it again to provide care.
How you should approach your negative zones
is to avoid the trigger,
for example, the person
I find exciting. It's not a good system because at
some point, and somehow, regarding them,
if you... then my
mind becomes like sandpaper, unpleasant.
What are the results of anger and
last month in Taiwan's Level 10?
I actually wanted to mention them.
How to avoid anger, the sea level 10,
mostly impossible anger in the kitchen.
If someone yells at you and you
understand the teacher, then you ca
n't get angry.
It's not that you avoid the anger,
but that the ultimate
solution for anger is to understand that
people who...  Irritated by Dirk U, there are
people who say everyone in the
group lies on them, yes, then
you say yes, life is a mirror, then
they would suddenly be completely silent,
everything that sees that, the percentage of
all irritating people is a, the
dirt is a direct mirror, you
irritate others, if you say 99 percent of the
people in Diamond Mountain irritate you,
then you say, I, their animals, 99 percent of
the people, well-trained
Buddhists, you can hate people
but tell because you do your art,
how you upset other people, because what
you see,
the percentage is the same, cleaning,
if you are 25% angry and you
go into a room with four people,
then one will make you, that
is higher middle school,
this would rather and therefore very
different group, high lamas and
also farmers, justice, he has to
adapt his, his ambassadors, something, he has to
teach under the school, and
we have a topic by Jan Treber
and it is about the fact that it is annoying,
kite, a very  A major
unique feature is that it takes all your
good seeds much more than
all other negative emotions to
really burn them.
We say yes, the chamber can
be destroyed, so we say, so how does he
reject them? Yes, you're right,
you will, they will never sprout. The same goes
for the negative ones, we tell ourselves, it's exactly the same
here with the positive ones.
You still have them, but they
will never give up.
That's just as bad as not
having them. It's all covered in the Mafia
literature. How can it be
that your good seeds are burned by anger?
What are the conditions
for this? There's
a big discussion about this, about
strange objects. Are you talking
about Buddhism or, aha,
the average person? What is it that
burns their bad seeds? If
you want to study this, there's still a little bit left.
I think the big problem,
the big problem with anger, is that it
destroys a good seed. Yes, you
can take them out of the refrigerator. There are
whole books about this. There's
one, because for that, a forest
fire should be normal.
If you meditate this afternoon, this week...
You can simply meditate with the pictures, it
's very effective.
After you've had your nap today
and have time, meditate
on the forest fire. If your husband is yelling at you,
tell him my philosophy because you're an [ __ ]. You
shouldn't get angry,
and I didn't do anything. You wanted it from me,
and you're a hero, and so on.
But I'm going to use up the
credit of a Gothic seed with a
Volcanic seed. I wo
n't get angry.
I hate you so much. I'm just going to ignore you.
I won't get angry. You don't
deserve to be the
person.
Joint account. The best way
to show anger is to
stay cool, and for that, the people who annoy
you most took ice skating
and smiled. I would love to get angry, be angry,
but you deserve it. But
I don't want to use up my good seeds, don't
want to run them so
I can have a chance tomorrow.
You're not even the ones who will be there. If
you
really want to annoy your enemy, then it's time to be
happy and successful.
He argues.  Don't mess with them online,
have fun in life, live a good life, and
that's the best way to
upset them. I'm special, we
do a little bit too, and then there's
a break. I told you, that
's a good way to
keep attention, to
promise a break, even if you don't do it yourself.
But when people kill each other,
when they fight, when they
attack each other online,
it's all caused by
negative emotions. Number two: anger.
This whole war destroys cities. I
love leaving
[Music].
I live in the smallest place, outwardly all of
Arizona, on a dirt road, and I've
spent a lot of time planting trees.
And it's just as hard as
teaching lambs and cattle, and you
need a lot of patience and many years to take care of
them. The deer should
n't be on the internet. Like a country
bombing people, it's bad enough,
but the trees... how hard
it is, how hard people work to get
a few trees to grow,
and you just become a bomb.
Anger is destructive;
it destroys as well as many years of work, a job
that takes to build a city.  Building,
raising children, and then
sending them to war to be killed is so
destructive. And it's just the
movement of the mind, thoughts that
destroy entire countries and tens of thousands
of people. Every person who dies
was labeled by their mother for years.
Mothers feed them, fathers
earn money, and then you send them to think
in a stupid war. I
was in a military academy and gave
a lecture.
Yeah, I'm going to be a Top Gun pilot,
and then they come home without feet, without legs.
And when don't you believe
in this fight, this fighter pilot fairytale?
A famous Rambo movie in
China. You should stop copying the bad
stuff from America, like
McDonald's, and not the toxic, these
violent movies. And that's
actually romantic. Top Gun isn't
romantic.
People come out of war without legs,
their whole lives are destroyed.
Alcohol isn't romantic. People in
movies and bringing them up isn't everything. It's
caused by that, and that's a
witty two-second thing.
If you're a...  If
you want to be a military man,
then fight in anger. In a
gar, if you can't control your anger, you
destroy countries
and make hundreds of thousands of people vulnerable.
I can already see it. But two times
promised, one line for another one
and one line from number two. Okay, tanks
on map against Kiel at the nuclear power plant contaminated,
odd Anniken's domicile,
because the water box, internet, in which one is
ours, there was in the Tibetan
monasteries. We should know that one needs it.
If you have a lama, it's the one who
often got upset, and in Buddhism, you shouldn't even
say anything bad about a tantric lama. Then suddenly there was
a secret language because if
you deal with a stingy lama, then
it meant only rugby, my lama. So
if you say, "And lama doesn't waste
money," then it actually means the
name is stingy. That's why there was
this second language in Tibet. This language, and
it's a language that offers the choice of
your lama expresses itself in a very polite way,
and so that the head of a
lama heats up.  Sometimes he
gets angry, often he gets angry
and hits the students. The heart—
excuse me, the heart of my holy
lama—gets warm, and that means he
often gets angry.
He hits us. I didn't have one like that often,
but sometimes. He had a
hot heart.
Maybe he played against Lothar a
little too hard. He was really an
honest person, and he said things
that other people don't want to talk about.
And we're talking about de
Bary incarnations. He looked them in the eye
and said, "Don't be
angry with your students." I wo
n't... A holy warm heart seed. Quite
honestly, you're a
bad role model.
You're a high-ranking lama in Canada,
and he said it out loud. That's why
he has so many problems, because he did that.
You can call them by a polite
name. And he's now quoting a
famous book. There's
only one more in between, the roughly
ten great ones, and the parts of the share. Then
taboo
Abu Dhabi, Qatar Ducato, Putin's
Christoffers in Sanskrit, Papa's double.
It is...  The spiritual aspect of the series
is an object, so it's called hard
practices, practically the hard practices
for the tough guys. Who's tougher there?
Grambow here, that's what was ordered. There's a
lama in Cadbury who stopped a train. The train
tried to start,
the lama stood in front of it, he pushed the train
back.
That's a tough guy, a tough
bloke, I'd say now. Or
meditating in the snow for two days, and a
spiritual fighter. And everyone is Moore. He stopped the train, meditated
in the snow for two days, and opened
his eyes. Reported, that's a
real lama from Shanti. The theme says
Donnersmarck.
That's not a tough bloke.
What's after Adam Hall? That's the wife
who comes home from work, the kitchen, the one who
opens it. The husband writes to her,
and she stays calm. That's a
spiritual fighter. Don't tell me anything
about people. In the snow, we see nothing
of the lama who stopped the train. That's
difficult in comparison, so that the word...
you stay calm when someone shouts at you.
Much harder than
sitting in the snow or stopping the train.
Staying calm in the kitchen when your
husband goes berserk, that's a
spiritual battle. It's the women
in the kitchen who mostly
take refuge and don't
scream back. That's a fighter. In America, there are
these war medals. I remember,
yes, these women in the
kitchen deserve the medal, not
the guys who go out and
kill others. Because in the kitchen, you need
the moon, a certain spiritual fighter.
It's the woman who doesn't yell at her husband
because she stops the screaming.
The people who stop the war
are braver. Those who stop
the war in their minds
have even more motives than those who stop the war in
the world.
You need more mother for that. That's
bad karma. Part of it is... what
is then number one? Anger. On all
bad karma, it's anger number one.
Why? Because it destroys all your good seeds.
Anger is number one on the
bad karma list. That's the
first line, and in the second and...
Patience is number one on the
spiritual fighter's list. It's much
harder than killing someone else
or throwing bombs.
You hold the weapon and move your
index finger. That's not hard. But
staying cool in the kitchen when you
argue for an hour, a day, or a month, and you stay calm,
that's a real fighter.
So if you can do it, then
you should be proud. Hopefully, if you stay in the
kitchen or when people
criticize each other online,
I won't risk my good seeds because of you.
I will
stay cool, and I won't
reply to you. [Pause] Page fighter. It
's very depressing to talk about these topics for so
long. We have
another task that I've already
mentioned today. We're now going to review the
last eight years,
and we're going to do it with pictures. You can
do this meditation in the afternoon
if you feel like it. You can do it in the
afternoon, and especially for those who
would like to become a teacher. If
you want to become a master, it's
unclear where you want to teach meditation.
Then these are for you.
I have to...  Quickly realize, but I just
talk so much, so I think these are the ones you should have
actually gone through in Thailand.
Sorry for so
much in Thailand, Tim. I'm at 78. This
is a young woman working on the computer.
We're repeating that lame rim in pictures.
I'll show you the pictures without the text.
Remember, we start tomorrow and I
'll test you.
I'll show the pictures and someone
say what this is about. You have to
try
to remember the pictures, the text, and the
pictures are here.
Maybe you'll have them
printed out by tomorrow. If you have music, the majority
to drive,
Jack Miller, he has fun.
She's a friend, Paige's number. She
tried to find the page number in
the translation that's related to the picture,
but if you really want to have fun,
then you can say it like this: this picture
refers to the page in the lamb in
the encounter at the beginning of the season.
This one before with the land. You start,
sold the land as a... It's a
first task to sell.
You have to show them how cool it is,
but see us.
In Buddhism, it's tradition that they
sell the content like before the
bug labs. It's just like selling a car.
The couple comes in, have you
noticed how great the stereo is in the
trigger?
The system is incomparable and
effective, and the wheels are Jörg Butt. We had to
talk about the cool stuff, and that's
tradition. And that's exactly where we are at the
moment. We have
n't gotten to the long one yet. Everyone, everyone,
87. We then have at the
beginning and are already there because they have disadvantages of the
choir barcodes. I have the Kossuth
place on her cheeks. 05. I first taught
the end of the lamb
meditation. Eight years ago, I had the
strategy.
I started at the end. We
studied the majority. We studied the
meditation of the emergency pass avatar and the
papas, and here we studied the end of the -
and we want to become the seeds
of the state association, and that's why
we have teacher-student spaces. That's why we studied
meditation.
We will now go into another  So,
I'm not going to repeat the end of this book,
but I'm going to
cover the same topic from Chiapas Labrador, APG of our long one. So, we've
already gone through all the pictures that are on the
Haid and meditation handle
because he doesn't want to
configure it. So, if the body
can only demand the topics,
no, at the point of sale, you can do
that. Yes, it's a lot and so
long, but you stood looking at it, which
somehow fits, and what's cool about the
picture is, we know who learns
in this picture,
the father in front. Okay, that the permanent teams of
why Muslims,
why does the daughter have to teach the father the
internet, wants to have expenses,
Pia's generation is like me doing the laundry,
Michael Kraus. It's very difficult,
I knew we had one evening, it's,
I would have you, and I asked what
is mostly not what, like chatting.
She took my phone and
uninstalled it again, just shut up.
You have a resistance and say
what tomorrow, it's uncomfortable for us, we do
n't know what it is.
I have God, which button do you have to
press to send an email?  Then tell me to
press the button.
That's the real reason I
have him, because he can teach himself all
those things. He's not afraid
of them.
He has the wonderful quality of
not being afraid of new technologies.
He calls the company and says the button is
n't working, and I'm more the
type who's afraid of that. And I think
even if I wait another three years, it's
old-fashioned and decided
not to learn this attitude
towards the country.
I'm not a [missing word], I'm not a [missing word], I
'm not a role.
I have my job, I have so much to do. I can't [missing word], I can't [missing word]
1000 [missing word] to
learn and meditate on. You reject
the act and this image
simultaneously means a form. Be like the father, what
combo? He was humble
and he asked his trainers.
I understand that with Facebook. Can you, can you please
explain it to me? What was
the new thing again? Well,
I already have my
Instagram today. Damn it, I'll do it. I
understand that it's too easy on the difficult
things. Appointment.
What do you say when I [missing word] the
picture?  Show that this is the new economy, you have
no actions, technology,
mosquito stop, making of the high score,
most people have, and then the
people who are up and don't say that's
just not
learning, because that besides, motive,
newspaper came,
the second key made because a
question, why am I only going to the marina for
information,
I said I'm not going,
Morphosys title, which means Bastille,
and I will have an eye, I will rise in the
ranking,
I want power,
I will then become a teacher and will be,
someone says you on your own life,
and that should be
these diseases, trouble, and Ammerland,
I will, that is the real mode,
teaching, earth of guilt, and if I can
defend myself, I am also
treated, should
I explain quantum physics, and
he is distracting,
where he can say no, Annika explains
everything wrong, that I explain, then I am
polite in English, have a conclusion,
system for him, it is, made, looks at,
or when exactly he helped,
I personally, he did it for you, there is
teach in tones, has a thousand users, has
before the midwives, mountain,
he gave the lecture, and it lasts
2000  I healed him angle 2009 10
the reason why you are right now because the
Buddha will be so you can read on
having a baby 2007 so you can clarify writes
the one driven in 2000 days said
conversations about a doctor [ __ ] the
future of the seas the future of
his mentality fashionable crime you
need you have you don't have a fixed Infineon
Street Days in three months so if
they give you one day then it's just
that is exactly what life crisis
wastes time pcs is and have to keep a
teacher at a
future
add
[Music]
I think an omniscient I think we
need right now Mascha has me
I will teach you whether you
want to or not tried to make him better
what was spoken last year
written out in national history
there are more computers of 130000 the
content really good and were not changed
it would not have survived if it was not
useful if it appeared that it was
made socially we wanted would have gone into
life already has an update
mission
it is a list of ok
I  I'm not telling you beforehand, I don't have time,
I know I have,
and when I hear that, I hear middle school
learning, I
'm 66 now, 20 or 30,
you're not allowed to be movies, Uncle, I'm
not saying how it is with us, to have
butyric acid to learn
so that you, I'm not saying that he
should be allowed to, you're tired of Mirasol, that
he has nothing else but when he's tired,
then I recommend you now, the cat,
I don't spend a whole day with that,
we have a house in any case, but after
two shopping trips, we've arrived, sometimes it's like, what's one called,
I
only work and yet we work in Spain,
then I work more, work than break,
I'm not against Canada, we're
now over the time and not because of
murder, continue with the 81, let your
husband kiss, let's first
imitate Luca Baldisserri
[Music]
the st
langula mandala came to me, yes Tajani
[Music]
so she took her drums,
so she took her boss
Bamberg
[Music]
with the lectures to give, and I
think tomorrow the Addams Family and
that  This is a repeat of the last
eight years
if you wanted to get certified in it.